## **Ezz Elden Mohamed**

## Front-end Web Developer

El Mansoura , El Dakahleya | 01002368023 , 01552282922 | ezzelden4work@gmail.com

My WebSite, linkedin , codepen , GitHub

## **Summary**

I'm a front-end web developer. I have 4 years of experience in this field. You can say that I'm a full-time Web developer in addition to being a student. I'm passionate about keeping up with everything new in technology trends, I have my personal touch at my work. you can be keen on me for any project you need to do.

### **Education**

I'm a student in the Delta Academy, I study at the faculty of Management Information Systems.

### Skills

Html | css | Javascript | jQuery | BootStrap | React js | Sass | GitHub | CssAnimation | AdobeXD | Figma | styled component | Reduxs| Php

# **Professional Experience**

<u>Atheltree</u>	2020 - 2021
Front-end Web Developer	
<ul><li>The Lean</li><li>Front-end Web Developer</li><li>Front-end Team Leader</li></ul>	2020 - 2020
<ul><li>Afro Arab Digital</li><li>Front-end Web Developer</li><li>Front-end Team Leader</li></ul>	2020 - 2020
<u>Devolum</u>	2018 - 2020

• Front-end Web Developer

# **Projects**

Vuesax Dashboard <u>gitHub</u> <u>Live View</u>

- Chart Plugin
- Dark & Light Mode
- Chat Page

#### Round Base

<u>gitHub</u> <u>Live View</u>

- React
- Company Review

See More Projects.....

# Internships

### Web Instructor:

I was giving some web development courses in my college by assembling groups of students and starting how to develop the website professionally.

## **Graduation project Assistant:**

I was assisting students in their graduation projects, supervising them in the design and development stages, and discussing them in front of a specialized committee of doctors in the fields of technology.

### Some of Project:

- Elfahd Elevetor
- Elmafgod Mawgod
- Smart Parking

# Langues

Arabic: Native | English: Good Write and Speak